let uscapitals = [
	{
		front: 'Alabama',
		back: 'Montgomery',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Alaska',
		back: 'Juneau',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Arizona',
		back: 'Phoenix',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Arkansas',
		back: 'Little Rock',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'California',
		back: 'Sacramento',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Colorado',
		back: 'Denver',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Connecticut',
		back: 'Hartford',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Delaware',
		back: 'Dover',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Florida',
		back: 'Tallahassee',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Georgia',
		back: 'Atlanta',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Hawaii',
		back: 'Honolulu',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Idaho',
		back: 'Boise',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Illinois',
		back: 'Springfield',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Indiana',
		back: 'Indianapolis',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Iowa',
		back: 'Des Moines',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Kansas',
		back: 'Topeka',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Kentucky',
		back: 'Frankfort',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Louisiana',
		back: 'Baton Rouge',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Maine',
		back: 'Augusta',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Maryland',
		back: 'Annapolis',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Massachusetts',
		back: 'Boston',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Michigan',
		back: 'Lansing',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Minnesota',
		back: 'Saint Paul',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Mississippi',
		back: 'Jackson',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Missouri',
		back: 'Jefferson City',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Montana',
		back: 'Helena',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Nebraska',
		back: 'Lincoln',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Nevada',
		back: 'Carson City',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'New Hampshire',
		back: 'Concord',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'New Jersey',
		back: 'Trenton',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'New Mexico',
		back: 'Santa Fe',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'New York',
		back: 'Albany',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'North Carolina',
		back: 'Raleigh',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'North Dakota',
		back: 'Bismark',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Ohio',
		back: 'Columbus',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Oklahoma',
		back: 'Oklahoma City',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Oregon',
		back: 'Salem',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Pennsylvania',
		back: 'Harrisburg',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Rhode Island',
		back: 'Providence',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'South Carolina',
		back: 'Columbia',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'South Dakota',
		back: 'Pierre',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Tennessee',
		back: 'Nashville',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Texas',
		back: 'Austin',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Utah',
		back: 'Salt Lake City',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Vermont',
		back: 'Montpelier',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Virginia',
		back: 'Richmond',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Washington',
		back: 'Olympia',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'West Virginia',
		back: 'Charleston',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Wisconsin',
		back: 'Madison',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
	{
		front: 'Wyoming',
		back: 'Cheyenne',
		tags: ['State Capitals'],
		score: 1,
	},
];
